<root>
	<static_icon id = "TCL">
		<img>../images/esticker/TCL.png</img>
	</static_icon>
	<static_icon id = "TCL_right">
		<img>../images/esticker/TCL_right.png</img>
	</static_icon>

	<icon id = "Smart">
		<img_L>../images/esticker/Esticker_SMART_B_l.png</img_L>
		<img_R>../images/esticker/Esticker_SMART_B_r.png</img_R>
		<img_S>../images/esticker/esticker_smart.png</img_S>
		<title>
			<Arabic>SMART</Arabic>
			<ArabicEgypt>SMART</ArabicEgypt>
			<English>SMART</English>
			<English_LA>SMART</English_LA>
			<English_NA>SMART</English_NA>
			<Chinese>SMART</Chinese>
			<ChineseTraditional>SMART</ChineseTraditional>
			<Bulgarian>SMART</Bulgarian>
			<Croatian>SMART</Croatian>
			<Czech>SMART</Czech>
			<Danish>SMART</Danish>
			<Dutch>SMART</Dutch>
			<Estonian>SMART</Estonian>
			<Finnish>DSMART</Finnish>
			<French>SMART</French>
			<German>SMART</German>
			<Greek>SMART</Greek>
			<Hungarian>SMART</Hungarian>
			<Hebrew>SMART</Hebrew>
			<Indonesian>SMART</Indonesian>
			<Italian>SMART</Italian>
			<Latvian>SMART</Latvian>
			<Lithuanian>SMART</Lithuanian>
			<Mongolian>SMART</Mongolian>
			<Norwegian>SMART</Norwegian>
			<Persian>SMART</Persian>
			<Polish>SMART</Polish>
			<Portuguese>SMART</Portuguese>
			<Portuguese_LA>SMART</Portuguese_LA>
			<Romanian>SMART</Romanian>
			<Russian>SMART</Russian>
			<Serbian>SMART</Serbian>
			<Slovak>SMART</Slovak>
			<Slovenian>SMART</Slovenian>
			<Spanish>SMART</Spanish>
			<Spanish_LA>SMART</Spanish_LA>
			<Spanish_NA>SMART</Spanish_NA>
			<Swedish>SMART</Swedish>
			<Turkish>SMART</Turkish>
			<Ukrainian>SMART</Ukrainian>
			<Thai>SMART</Thai>
			<Uzbek>SMART</Uzbek>
			<Vietnamese>SMART</Vietnamese>
		</title>
		<description>
			<Arabic>يحتوي التليفزيون الذكي على وظائف متقدمة وخيارات محتوى غنية ليتناسب مع نمط حباتك اليومية. طريقة أسرع وأيسر وأكثر ذكاءً لمساعدتك على تصفح المحتوى.</Arabic>
			<ArabicEgypt>يحتوي التلفاز الذكي على وظائف متطورة وخيارات محتوى متعددة لتناسب نمط حياتك اليومية. طريقة أكثر ذكاءً وأسهل وأسرع مخصصة لك لتصفح المحتوى.</ArabicEgypt>
			<English>Smart TV contains upgraded functions and rich content options to fit your daily lifestyle. Smarter, easier, faster and a more intelligent way for you to surf content.</English>
			<English_LA>Smart TV contains upgraded functions and rich content options to fit your daily lifestyle. Smarter, easier, faster and a more intelligent way for you to surf content.</English_LA>
			<English_NA>Smart TV contains upgraded functions and rich content options to fit your daily lifestyle. Smarter, easier, faster and a more intelligent way for you to surf content.</English_NA>
			<Chinese>Smart,easier,faster and a more intelligent way to surf content on a single device or across multiple devices. Smart TVs contain upgraded functions designed with rich content to completely suit your lifestyle.</Chinese>
			<ChineseTraditional>Smart,easier,faster and a more intelligent way to surf content on a single device or across multiple devices. Smart TVs contain upgraded functions designed with rich content to completely suit your lifestyle.</ChineseTraditional>
			<Bulgarian>Абонирайте се да гледате хиляди нови, стари и класически телевизионни предавания и филми с натискане на един бутон.</Bulgarian>
			<Croatian>Pretplatite se i gledajte na tisuće novih, starih i klasičnih TV emisija i filmova na dohvat ruke.</Croatian>
			<Czech>Přihlaste se a na dosah ruky budete mít sledování tisíců nových, starých i klasických televizních show a filmů.</Czech>
			<Danish>Registrer dig for at se tusinder af nye, gamle og klassiske tv-shows og film, lige når du har lyst.</Danish>
			<Dutch>Neem een abonnement en bekijk duizenden nieuwe, oude en klassieke TV-shows en films wanneer u maar wilt.</Dutch>
			<Estonian>Registreeru tuhandete uute, vanade ja klassikaks saanud telesaadete ning filmide vaatamiseks.</Estonian>
			<Finnish>Tilaa katseluoikeus tuhansiin uusiin, vanhoihin ja perinteisiin TV-ohjelmiin ja elokuviin, jotka ovat käden ulottuvilla.</Finnish>
			<French>Avec ses fonctionnalités améliorées et ses options de contenu riche, le téléviseur Smart saura convenir à votre mode de vie quotidien. Une façon plus intelligente, plus facile et plus rapide de naviguer le contenu.</French>
			<German>Abonnieren Sie Tausende neuer, alter und klassischer Fernsehsendungen und Filme mit den Fingerspitzen.</German>
			<Greek>Εγγραφείτε για να παρακολουθείτε εύκολα και γρήγορα χιλιάδες καινούργιες, παλιές και κλασικές τηλεοπτικές εκπομπές και ταινίες.</Greek>
			<Hungarian>Előfizetve több ezer új, régi és klasszikus, Önnek csak karnyújtásnyira lévő TV-műsort és filmet tekinthet meg.</Hungarian>
			<Hebrew>הטלוויזיה החכמה כוללת שדרוגים ואפשרויות תוכן מועשר שיתאימו לאורח החיים היומיומי שלך. זו דרך חכמה יותר, קלה יותר לשימוש, מהירה יותר ואינטליגנטית יותר עבורך לגלוש בין תכנים.</Hebrew>
			<Indonesian>TV Pintar dilengkapi fungsi yang lebih baik dan pilihan konten yang lebih kaya untuk memenuhi gaya hidup keseharian Anda. Sekarang, Anda dapat menavigasi konten dengan lebih pintar, lebih mudah, lebih cepat, dan lebih cerdas.</Indonesian>
			<Italian>Iscriviti per avere sempre a portata di mano migliaia di film e programmi TV nuovi, vecchi e i classici.</Italian>
			<Latvian>Abonējiet un skatieties tūkstošiem jaunu, vecu un klasisku TV šovu un filmu, kas pieejami nekavējoties.</Latvian>
			<Lithuanian>Užsiprenumeruokite ir žiūrėkite tūkstančius naujų, senų ir klasikinių TV laidų ir filmų – tai ranka pasiekiama.</Lithuanian>
			<Mongolian>Ухаалаг ТВ нь таны өдөр тутмын амьдралд зохицсон сайжруулсан үйлдлүүд, өргөн контентын сонголттой. Хөтөлбөрөө илүү ухаалаг, илүү хялбар, илүү хурдан сонгон үзэх арга.</Mongolian>
			<Norwegian>Abonner for å se tusenvis av nye, gamle og klassiske TV-show og filmer der du er.</Norwegian>
			<Persian>تلویزیون هوشمند دارای قابلیت های ارتقایافته و برنامه های متنوعی است که با سبک زندگی روزانه شما مطابقت خواهد داشت. روشی هوشمندانه تر، آسان تر و سریعتر برای مشاهده برنامه ها و محتواها.</Persian>
			<Polish>Zasubskrybuj, aby uzyskać dostęp do tysięcy nowych, starych i klasycznych seriali i filmów.</Polish>
			<Portuguese>A Smart TV contêm funções atualizadas e opções com conteúdos ricos que se adaptam ao seu estilo de vida diário. Uma forma mais fácil, rápida e inteligente de navegar pelos conteúdos.</Portuguese>
			<Portuguese_LA>As Smart TVs contêm funções aprimoradas e opções com conteúdo rico para atender ao seu estilo de vida no dia a dia. Uma maneira mais moderna, fácil, rápida e inteligente para você navegar por conteúdos.</Portuguese_LA>
			<Romanian>Abonaţi-vă şi urmăriţi mii de seriale şi filme TV vechi şi clasice, toate la îndemâna dvs.</Romanian>
			<Russian>Смарт-телевизоры обладают новейшими функциями и средствами отображения контента, разработанными для полного удовлетворения возросших потребностей вашего повседневного образа жизни. Вам предоставляется более интеллектуальный, простой и быстрый способ поиска контента.</Russian>
			<Serbian>Prijavite se i moći ćete da gledate hiljade novih, starih i klasičnih TV emisija, serija i filmova – sve će vam biti nadohvat ruke.</Serbian>
			<Slovak>Odoberanie tisícok nových, starých a klasických TV relácií a filmov na dosah rúk.</Slovak>
			<Slovenian>Prijavite se za gledanje novih, starih in klasičnih TV oddaj in filmov, ki so vam na dosegu roke.</Slovenian>
			<Spanish>El Smart TV contiene funciones actualizadas y una variedad de opciones de contenido que se adaptan a tu estilo de vida diario. Más inteligente, más fácil, más rápido. Una forma más inteligente de navegar por los contenidos.</Spanish>
			<Spanish_LA>El Smart TV contiene funciones actualizadas y una variedad de opciones de contenido que se adaptan a tu estilo de vida diario. Más inteligente, más fácil, más rápido. Una forma más inteligente de navegar por los contenidos.</Spanish_LA>
			<Spanish_NA>El Smart TV contiene funciones actualizadas y una variedad de opciones de contenido que se adaptan a tu estilo de vida diario. Más inteligente, más fácil, más rápido. Una forma más inteligente de navegar por los contenidos.</Spanish_NA>
			<Swedish>Prenumerera för att visa tusentals nya, gamla och klassiska TV-program och filmer genom bara en fingertoppstryckning.</Swedish>
			<Turkish>İyi bildiğiniz binlerce yeni, eski ve klasik TV gösterilerini ve filmlerini izlemek için abone olun.</Turkish>
			<Thai>Smart TV มีตัวเลือกฟังก์ชั่นที่อัพเกรดแล้วและเนื้อหาหลากหลายที่เหมาะกับไลฟ์สไตล์ในแต่ละวันของคุณ ด้วยวิธีการที่ฉลาด ง่าย เร็ว และอัจฉริยะยิ่งขึ้นสำหรับคุณในการเปิดดูเนื้อหา</Thai>
			<Ukrainian>Здійсніть передплату для простого перегляду тисяч нових, старих та класичних телешоу і кінофільмів.</Ukrainian>
			<Uzbek>Smart TV kundalik yashash tarzingizga mos kelishi uchun yangilangan funksiyalar va boy kontent opsiyalariga egadir. Kontentlarni ko‘rib chiqishingiz uchun tartibliroq, osonroq, tezroq va aqlliroq usul.</Uzbek>
			<Vietnamese>TV thông minh có các chức năng nâng cao và nhiều lựa chọn nội dung phong phú phù hợp với cách sống của bạn. Là phương tiện giúp lưới nội dung của bạn thông minh, dễ dàng, nhanh chóng và tiện lợi hơn.</Vietnamese>
		</description>
	</icon>

	<icon id = "Netflix">
		<img_L>../images/esticker/Esticker_Netflix_B_l.png</img_L>
		<img_R>../images/esticker/Esticker_Netflix_B_r.png</img_R>
		<img_S>../images/esticker/esticker_netflix.png</img_S>
		<title>
			<Arabic>NETFLIX</Arabic>
			<ArabicEgypt>NETFLIX</ArabicEgypt>
			<English>NETFLIX</English>
			<English_LA>NETFLIX</English_LA>
			<English_NA>NETFLIX</English_NA>
			<Chinese>NETFLIX</Chinese>
			<ChineseTraditional>NETFLIX</ChineseTraditional>
			<Bulgarian>NETFLIX</Bulgarian>
			<Croatian>NETFLIX</Croatian>
			<Czech>NETFLIX</Czech>
			<Danish>NETFLIX</Danish>
			<Dutch>NETFLIX</Dutch>
			<Estonian>NETFLIX</Estonian>
			<Finnish>DNETFLIX</Finnish>
			<French>NETFLIX</French>
			<German>NETFLIX</German>
			<Greek>NETFLIX</Greek>
			<Hungarian>NETFLIX</Hungarian>
			<Hebrew>נטפליקס</Hebrew>
			<Indonesian>NETFLIX</Indonesian>
			<Italian>NETFLIX</Italian>
			<Latvian>NETFLIX</Latvian>
			<Lithuanian>NETFLIX</Lithuanian>
			<Mongolian>NETFLIX</Mongolian>
			<Norwegian>NETFLIX</Norwegian>
			<Persian>NETFLIX</Persian>
			<Polish>NETFLIX</Polish>
			<Portuguese>NETFLIX</Portuguese>
			<Portuguese_LA>NETFLIX</Portuguese_LA>
			<Romanian>NETFLIX</Romanian>
			<Russian>NETFLIX</Russian>
			<Serbian>NETFLIX</Serbian>
			<Slovak>NETFLIX</Slovak>
			<Slovenian>NETFLIX</Slovenian>
			<Spanish>NETFLIX</Spanish>
			<Spanish_LA>NETFLIX</Spanish_LA>
			<Spanish_NA>NETFLIX</Spanish_NA>
			<Swedish>NETFLIX</Swedish>
			<Turkish>NETFLIX</Turkish>
			<Ukrainian>NETFLIX</Ukrainian>
			<Thai>NETFLIX</Thai>
			<Uzbek>NETFLIX</Uzbek>
			<Vietnamese>NETFLIX</Vietnamese>
		</title>
		<description>
			<Arabic>ضم نتفليكس (Netflix) مجموعة واسعة من المحتوى الشائع حيث يمكن تحقيق المتعة للجميع. يمكنك مشاهدة العروض التليفزيونية الموصى بها، و أحدث الأفلام الوثائقية والمسلسلات وأفلام نتفليكس (Netflix) الأصلية الحاصلة على الجوائز. </Arabic>
			<ArabicEgypt>تمتلك نتفليكس مجموعة كبيرة من المحتوى الشائع الذي يناسب الجميع. يمكنك مشاهدة البرامج التلفزيونية الموصى بها، ومسلسلات نتفليكس الأصلية الحائزة على جوائز، وأحدث الأفلام، والأفلام الوثائقية.</ArabicEgypt>
			<English>Netflix has a huge range of popular content for everyone. You can watch recommended TV shows, award-winning Netflix original series, latest movies, and documentaries.</English>
			<English_LA>Netflix has a huge range of popular content for everyone. You can watch recommended TV shows, award-winning Netflix original series, latest movies, and documentaries.</English_LA>
			<English_NA>Netflix has a huge range of popular content for everyone. You can watch recommended TV shows, award-winning Netflix original series, latest movies, and documentaries.</English_NA>
			<Chinese>As one of the world's leading internet television with a huge range of popular content, Netflix has something for everyone. You can watch TV shows recommended just for you, including award-winning Netflix original series, movies, and documentaries.</Chinese>
			<ChineseTraditional>As one of the world's leading internet television with a huge range of popular content, Netflix has something for everyone. You can watch TV shows recommended just for you, including award-winning Netflix original series, movies, and documentaries.</ChineseTraditional>
			<Bulgarian>Абонирайте се да гледате хиляди нови, стари и класически телевизионни предавания и филми с натискане на един бутон.</Bulgarian>
			<Croatian>Pretplatite se i gledajte na tisuće novih, starih i klasičnih TV emisija i filmova na dohvat ruke.</Croatian>
			<Czech>Přihlaste se a na dosah ruky budete mít sledování tisíců nových, starých i klasických televizních show a filmů.</Czech>
			<Danish>Registrer dig for at se tusinder af nye, gamle og klassiske tv-shows og film, lige når du har lyst.</Danish>
			<Dutch>Neem een abonnement en bekijk duizenden nieuwe, oude en klassieke TV-shows en films wanneer u maar wilt.</Dutch>
			<Estonian>Registreeru tuhandete uute, vanade ja klassikaks saanud telesaadete ning filmide vaatamiseks.</Estonian>
			<Finnish>Tilaa katseluoikeus tuhansiin uusiin, vanhoihin ja perinteisiin TV-ohjelmiin ja elokuviin, jotka ovat käden ulottuvilla.</Finnish>
			<French>Netflix a une énorme gamme de contenu populaire couvrant tous les goûts. Vous pouvez regarder des émissions de télévision recommandées, des séries originales primées de Netflix, les derniers films et des documentaires.</French>
			<German>Abonnieren Sie Tausende neuer, alter und klassischer Fernsehsendungen und Filme mit den Fingerspitzen.</German>
			<Greek>Εγγραφείτε για να παρακολουθείτε εύκολα και γρήγορα χιλιάδες καινούργιες, παλιές και κλασικές τηλεοπτικές εκπομπές και ταινίες.</Greek>
			<Hungarian>Előfizetve több ezer új, régi és klasszikus, Önnek csak karnyújtásnyira lévő TV-műsort és filmet tekinthet meg.</Hungarian>
			<Hebrew>לנטפליקס יש מגוון עצום של תוכן פופולארי שמתאים לכולם. באפשרותך לצפות בתוכניות טלוויזיה מומלצות, בסדרות מקוריות עטורות פרסים מבית נטפליקס, בסרטים חדשים ובסרטים תיעודיים.</Hebrew>
			<Indonesian>Netflix punya segudang konten populer untuk setiap orang. Anda dapat menyaksikan acara TV yang direkomendasikan, serial orisinil Netflix pemenang berbagai penghargaan, film terbaru, serta dokumenter.</Indonesian>
			<Italian>Iscriviti per avere sempre a portata di mano migliaia di film e programmi TV nuovi, vecchi e i classici.</Italian>
			<Latvian>Abonējiet un skatieties tūkstošiem jaunu, vecu un klasisku TV šovu un filmu, kas pieejami nekavējoties.</Latvian>
			<Lithuanian>Užsiprenumeruokite ir žiūrėkite tūkstančius naujų, senų ir klasikinių TV laidų ir filmų – tai ranka pasiekiama.</Lithuanian>
			<Mongolian>Netflix нь бүх хүнд зориулсан маш өргөн хүрээтэй, алдартай контентууд агуулдаг.  Та тэдний санал болгосон ТВ шоу, Netflix-ийн шагналт оригинал цуврал, хамгийн сүүлийн үеийн кино, баримтат киноноос үзэх боломжтой.</Mongolian>
			<Norwegian>Abonner for å se tusenvis av nye, gamle og klassiske TV-show og filmer der du er.</Norwegian>
			<Persian>Netflix برنامه بسیاری متنوعی برای همگان دارد. می توانید سریال های تلویزیونی پیشنهادی، سریال های تقدیر شده تولید Netflix، جدیدترین فیلم ها و مستندها را تماشا کنید.</Persian>
			<Polish>Zasubskrybuj, aby uzyskać dostęp do tysięcy nowych, starych i klasycznych seriali i filmów.</Polish>
			<Portuguese>A Netflix tem uma vasta gama de populares conteúdos para todos. Pode ver programas de TV recomendados e as galardoadas séries originais da Netflix, os filmes mais recentes e documentários.</Portuguese>
			<Portuguese_LA>A Netflix tem uma grande variedade de conteúdo popular para todas as pessoas. Você pode assistir a programas de TV recomendados, premiadas séries originais da Netflix, aos filmes mais atuais e documentários.</Portuguese_LA>
			<Romanian>Abonaţi-vă şi urmăriţi mii de seriale şi filme TV vechi şi clasice, toate la îndemâna dvs.</Romanian>
			<Russian>Netflix имеет огромный выбор популярных программ для каждого пользователя. Вы можете смотреть телепередачи, рекомендуемые специально для вас, включая превосходные сериалы Netflix, а также последние художественные и документальные фильмы.</Russian>
			<Serbian>Prijavite se i moći ćete da gledate hiljade novih, starih i klasičnih TV emisija, serija i filmova – sve će vam biti nadohvat ruke.</Serbian>
			<Slovak>Odoberanie tisícok nových, starých a klasických TV relácií a filmov na dosah rúk.</Slovak>
			<Slovenian>Prijavite se za gledanje novih, starih in klasičnih TV oddaj in filmov, ki so vam na dosegu roke.</Slovenian>
			<Spanish>Netflix ofrece una amplia variedad de contenido popular para todos. Puede ver programas de televisión recomendados, series originales y premiadas de Netflix, películas de estreno y documentales.</Spanish>
			<Spanish_LA>Netflix ofrece una amplia variedad de contenido popular para todos. Puede ver programas de televisión recomendados, series originales y premiadas de Netflix, películas de estreno y documentales.</Spanish_LA>
			<Spanish_NA>Netflix ofrece una amplia variedad de contenido popular para todos. Puede ver programas de televisión recomendados, series originales y premiadas de Netflix, películas de estreno y documentales.</Spanish_NA>
			<Swedish>Prenumerera för att visa tusentals nya, gamla och klassiska TV-program och filmer genom bara en fingertoppstryckning.</Swedish>
			<Turkish>İyi bildiğiniz binlerce yeni, eski ve klasik TV gösterilerini ve filmlerini izlemek için abone olun.</Turkish>
			<Thai>Netflix มีเนื้อหายอดนิยมที่หลากหลายสำหรับทุกคน คุณสามารถรับชมรายการ TV, ซีรี่ส์ต้นฉบับของ Netflix ที่ได้รับรางวัล, ภาพยนตร์ล่าสุด และ สารคดีที่เราแนะนำ</Thai>
			<Ukrainian>Здійсніть передплату для простого перегляду тисяч нових, старих та класичних телешоу і кінофільмів.</Ukrainian>
			<Uzbek>Netflix har bir kishi uchun juda katta hajmdagi ommabop kontentlarga ega. Siz tavsiya qilingan TV shoular, sovrinlar bilan taqdirlangan asl Netflix seriallari, yangi kinofimlar va hujjatli filmlarni ko‘rishingiz mumkin.</Uzbek>
			<Vietnamese>Netflix có nhiều nội dung phong phú đáp ứng mọi lưới tuổi. Bạn có thể xem các chương trình TV được đề xuất, những loạt chương trình nguyên gốc từng giành giải thưởng của Netflix và phim truyện và phim tài liệu mới nhất.</Vietnamese>
		</description>
	</icon>

	<icon id = "YouTube">
		<img_L>../images/esticker/Esticker_Youtube_B_l.png</img_L>
		<img_R>../images/esticker/Esticker_Youtube_B_r.png</img_R>
		<img_S>../images/esticker/esticker_youtube.png</img_S>
		<title>
			<Arabic>YouTube</Arabic>
			<ArabicEgypt>يوتيوب</ArabicEgypt>
			<English>YouTube</English>
			<English_LA>YouTube</English_LA>
			<English_NA>YouTube</English_NA>
			<Chinese>YouTube</Chinese>
			<ChineseTraditional>YouTube</ChineseTraditional>
			<Bulgarian>YouTube</Bulgarian>
			<Croatian>YouTube</Croatian>
			<Czech>YouTube</Czech>
			<Danish>YouTube</Danish>
			<Dutch>YouTube</Dutch>
			<Estonian>YouTube</Estonian>
			<Finnish>YouTube</Finnish>
			<French>YouTube</French>
			<German>YouTube</German>
			<Greek>YouTube</Greek>
			<Hungarian>YouTube</Hungarian>
			<Hebrew>YouTube</Hebrew>
			<Indonesian>YouTube</Indonesian>
			<Italian>YouTube</Italian>
			<Latvian>YouTube</Latvian>
			<Lithuanian>YouTube</Lithuanian>
			<Mongolian>YouTube</Mongolian>
			<Norwegian>YouTube</Norwegian>
			<Persian>YouTube</Persian>
			<Polish>YouTube</Polish>
			<Portuguese>YouTube</Portuguese>
			<Portuguese_LA>YouTube</Portuguese_LA>
			<Romanian>YouTube</Romanian>
			<Russian>YouTube</Russian>
			<Serbian>YouTube</Serbian>
			<Slovak>YouTube</Slovak>
			<Slovenian>YouTube</Slovenian>
			<Spanish>YouTube</Spanish>
			<Spanish_LA>YouTube</Spanish_LA>
			<Spanish_NA>YouTube</Spanish_NA>
			<Swedish>YouTube</Swedish>
			<Turkish>YouTube</Turkish>
			<Ukrainian>YouTube</Ukrainian>
			<Thai>YouTube</Thai>
			<Uzbek>YouTube</Uzbek>
			<Vietnamese>YouTube</Vietnamese>
		</title>
		<description>
			<Arabic>مع يوتيوب (YouTube) يمكنك مشاهدة ما يشاهده العالم - من مقاطع الفيديو الموسيقية الأكثر إثارة إلى الألعاب الأكثر جذبًا والتسلية والأحبار وغير ذلك الكثير.</Arabic>
			<ArabicEgypt>باستخدام YouTube، يمكنك التعرف على ما يشاهده العالم - بدءًا من أحدث مقاطع فيديو الموسيقى وصولاً إلى ما الجديد في الألعاب والترفيه والأخبار والمزيد.</ArabicEgypt>
			<English>With YouTube, you can see what the world is watching – from the hottest music videos to what's trending in gaming, entertainment, news and more.</English>
			<English_LA>With YouTube, you can see what the world is watching – from the hottest music videos to what's trending in gaming, entertainment, news and more.</English_LA>
			<English_NA>With YouTube, you can see what the world is watching – from the hottest music videos to what's trending in gaming, entertainment, news and more.</English_NA>
			<Chinese>With YouTube, you can see what the world is watching – from the hottest music videos to what's trending in gaming, entertainment, news and more. Subscribe to channels you love, share with friends, and view on any device.</Chinese>
			<ChineseTraditional>With YouTube, you can see what the world is watching – from the hottest music videos to what's trending in gaming, entertainment, news and more. Subscribe to channels you love, share with friends, and view on any device.</ChineseTraditional>
			<Bulgarian>With YouTube, you can see what the world is watching – from the hottest music videos to what's trending in gaming, entertainment, news and more. Subscribe to channels you love, share with friends, and view on any device.</Bulgarian>
			<Croatian>With YouTube, you can see what the world is watching – from the hottest music videos to what's trending in gaming, entertainment, news and more. Subscribe to channels you love, share with friends, and view on any device.</Croatian>
			<Czech>With YouTube, you can see what the world is watching – from the hottest music videos to what's trending in gaming, entertainment, news and more. Subscribe to channels you love, share with friends, and view on any device.</Czech>
			<Danish>With YouTube, you can see what the world is watching – from the hottest music videos to what's trending in gaming, entertainment, news and more. Subscribe to channels you love, share with friends, and view on any device.</Danish>
			<Dutch>With YouTube, you can see what the world is watching – from the hottest music videos to what's trending in gaming, entertainment, news and more. Subscribe to channels you love, share with friends, and view on any device.</Dutch>
			<Estonian>With YouTube, you can see what the world is watching – from the hottest music videos to what's trending in gaming, entertainment, news and more. Subscribe to channels you love, share with friends, and view on any device.</Estonian>
			<Finnish>With YouTube, you can see what the world is watching – from the hottest music videos to what's trending in gaming, entertainment, news and more. Subscribe to channels you love, share with friends, and view on any device.</Finnish>
			<French>Avec YouTube, vous pouvez voir ce que le monde regarde – des vidéos de musique les plus branchées à ce qui fait la une en jeux, divertissement, nouvelles, et plus.</French>
			<German>With YouTube, you can see what the world is watching – from the hottest music videos to what's trending in gaming, entertainment, news and more. Subscribe to channels you love, share with friends, and view on any device.</German>
			<Greek>Παρακολουθήστε δημοφιλή δωρεάν τηλεοπτικά κανάλια από ολόκληρο τον κόσμο με σύντομους χρόνους προσωρινής αποθήκευσης και ενημερώσεις πραγματικού χρόνου.</Greek>
			<Hungarian>Népszerű szabadon fogható (Free-to-Air) csatornákat nézhet a világ minden részéről, rövid pufferelési idők és valós idejű frissítések mellett.</Hungarian>
			<Hebrew>עם יוטיוב, תוכלו לצפות במה שהעולם צופה, כגון קליפי המוסיקה האחרונים ובמילה האחרונה בתחומי הגיימינג, הבידור, החדשות ועוד.</Hebrew>
			<Indonesian>Lewat YouTube, Anda dapat melihat apa yang dunia tonton - dari video musik populer terbaru hingga tren terbaru dalam dunia permainan, hiburan, berita, dan lain sebagainya.</Indonesian>
			<Italian>Guarda i famosi canali TV Free to Air in tutto il mondo, con brevissimi tempi di attesa e aggiornamenti in tempo reale.</Italian>
			<Latvian>Skatieties populārus brīvi uztveramus TV kanālus no visas pasaules ar īsiem buferizācijas laikiem un reāllaika atjauninājumiem.</Latvian>
			<Lithuanian>Žiūrėkite populiarius nemokamai transliuojamus TV kanalus iš viso pasaulio – trumpas buferizacijos laikas ir tikralaikiai naujiniai.</Lithuanian>
			<Mongolian>YouTube-ээр та дэлхийн хүмүүсийн үзэж буй зүйлсийг үзэх боломжтой - алдартай дууны клипнүүдээс эхлээд тоглоом, зугаа цэнгэл, мэдээ зэрэг тренд болж буй бусад олон зүйлс</Mongolian>
			<Norwegian>Se populære gratis TV-kanaler fra hele verden med korte buffertider og oppdateringer i sanntid.</Norwegian>
			<Persian>با YouTube می توانید تمام آنچه را به جهان به نظاره آن نشسته است تماشا کنید - از جدیدترین موزیک ویدیوها گرفته تا آخرین موضوعات داغ در جهان بازی های ویدیویی، تفریحات، اخبار و غیره.</Persian>
			<Polish>Oglądaj popularne kanały telewizyjne FTA z całego świata z krótkim czasem buforowania i aktualizacjami w czasie rzeczywistym.</Polish>
			<Portuguese>Com o YouTube, veja o que se passa no mundo – dos vídeos de música do momento às últimas tendências nos jogos, entretenimento, notícias e muito mais.</Portuguese>
			<Portuguese_LA>Com o YouTube, você pode ver o que o mundo todo está assistindo: dos vídeos de músicas mais atuais até o que está acontecendo em jogos, entretenimento, notícias e muito mais.</Portuguese_LA>
			<Romanian>Urmăriţi canale TV cu acces liber din toată lumea, cu timpi de buffering reduşi şi actualizări în timp real.</Romanian>
			<Russian>С YouTube вы можете увидеть все, что смотрит весь мир, в том числе самые горячие музыкальные клипы, новинки в мире игр и развлечений, новостные программы и многое другое.</Russian>
			<Serbian>Gledajte popularne otključane TV kanale iz svih krajeva sveta, koji se kratko baferuju i ažuriraju u realnom vremenu.</Serbian>
			<Slovak>Sledujte populárne TV kanály Free to Air z celého sveta s krátkymi dobami ukladania do medzipamäte a aktualizáciami v reálnom čase.</Slovak>
			<Slovenian>Predvajajte popularne brezplačne TV kanale iz celega sveta s kratkim časom nalaganja in posodobitvami v realnem času.</Slovenian>
			<Spanish>Con YouTube, puedes ver lo que el mundo ve: desde los videos musicales más exitosos hasta las últimas tendencias en videojuegos, entretenimiento, noticias y más.</Spanish>
			<Spanish_LA>Con YouTube, puedes ver lo que el mundo ve: desde los videos musicales más exitosos hasta las últimas tendencias en videojuegos, entretenimiento, noticias y más.</Spanish_LA>
			<Spanish_NA>Con YouTube, puedes ver lo que el mundo ve: desde los videos musicales más exitosos hasta las últimas tendencias en videojuegos, entretenimiento, noticias y más.</Spanish_NA>
			<Swedish>Se populära, gratis TV-kanaler från hela världen med korta bufferttider och realtidsuppdateringar.</Swedish>
			<Turkish>Dünyanın her yerinden popüler Ücretsiz Yayın Yapan TV kanallarını, kısa ara belleğe alma süreleri ve gerçek zamanlı güncellemeler ile izleyin.</Turkish>
			<Thai>เมื่อใช้ YouTube คุณสามารถดูได้ว่าคนทั้งโลกดูอะไรกัน – นับจากมิวสิควิดีโอยอดฮิตจนถึงแนวโน้มการเล่นเกม บันเทิง ข่าว และอื่น ๆ</Thai>
			<Ukrainian>Переглядайте популярні телеканали Free-to-Air з усього світу з коротким часом буферизації та оновленнями в реальному часі.</Ukrainian>
			<Uzbek>YouTube bilan siz butun dunyo ko‘rayotgan narsalarni – eng qaynoq musiqali videolardan tortib eng so‘nggi o‘yinlar, ko‘ngilochar dasturlar, yangiliklar kabilarni ko‘rishingiz mumkin.</Uzbek>
			<Vietnamese>Với YouTube, bạn có thể xem các nội dung hiện hành trên thế giới – từ các video âm nhạc nóng nhất cho tới xu hướng trong trò chơi, giải trí, tin tức và nhiều hơn thế.</Vietnamese>
		</description>
	</icon>

	<icon id = "App Store">
		<img_L>../images/esticker/Esticker_App store_B_l.png</img_L>
		<img_R>../images/esticker/Esticker_App store_B_r.png</img_R>
		<img_S>../images/esticker/esticker_appstore.png</img_S>
		<title>
			<Arabic>متجر التطبيقات</Arabic>
			<ArabicEgypt>متجر التطبيقات</ArabicEgypt>
			<English>App Store</English>
			<English_LA>App Store</English_LA>
			<English_NA>App Store</English_NA>
			<Chinese>App Store</Chinese>
			<ChineseTraditional>App Store</ChineseTraditional>
			<Bulgarian>Подобрява изживяването при гледане на спортни състезания</Bulgarian>
			<Croatian>Unaprijedite sportski doživljaj gledanja</Croatian>
			<Czech>Lepší zážitek ze sledování sportu</Czech>
			<Danish>Forbedret visning af sportsprogrammer</Danish>
			<Dutch>Verbeterde ervaring tijdens het kijken van sport</Dutch>
			<Estonian>Parem spordisaadete vaatamine</Estonian>
			<Finnish>Parantaa urheiluohjelmien katsomista</Finnish>
			<French>App Store</French>
			<German>Verbesserte Unterhaltung bei Sportsendungen</German>
			<Greek>Βελτιωμένη εμπειρία θέασης αθλημάτων</Greek>
			<Hungarian>Élménydúsabb sportközvetítés</Hungarian>
			<Hebrew>חנות אפליקציות</Hebrew>
			<Indonesian>Toko apl</Indonesian>
			<Italian>Miglioramento dell'esperienza visiva dei programmi sportivi</Italian>
			<Latvian>Uzlabojiet sporta skatīšanās pieredzi</Latvian>
			<Lithuanian>Pagerinta sporto žiūrėjimo patirtis</Lithuanian>
			<Mongolian>App Store</Mongolian>
			<Norwegian>Forbedret opplevelse for sportsinnhold</Norwegian>
			<Persian>فروشگاه نرم افزار</Persian>
			<Polish>Lepsze oglądanie sportu</Polish>
			<Portuguese>Loja de Apps</Portuguese>
			<Portuguese_LA>Loja de Apps</Portuguese_LA>
			<Romanian>Special pentru fanii sporturilor...</Romanian>
			<Russian>App Store</Russian>
			<Serbian>Bolji doživljaj gledanja sporskih sadržaja</Serbian>
			<Slovak>Vylepšenie zážitku zo sledovania športu</Slovak>
			<Slovenian>Izboljšajte izkušnjo spremljanja športa</Slovenian>
			<Spanish>App Store</Spanish>
			<Spanish_LA>App Store</Spanish_LA>
			<Spanish_NA>App Store</Spanish_NA>
			<Swedish>Bättre sportvisningsupplevelse</Swedish>
			<Turkish>Spor izleme deneyiminizi geliştirin</Turkish>
			<Ukrainian>Покращений перегляд спортивних передач</Ukrainian>
			<Thai>App Store</Thai>
			<Uzbek>Ilovalar do‘koni</Uzbek>
			<Vietnamese>App Store</Vietnamese>
		</title>
		<description>
			<Arabic>يقدم متجر التطبيقات أكثر من 300 تطبيقًا تبدأ من فيديو حسب الطلب و التطبيقات الاجتماعية والألعاب والموسيقى ومشاركة الصور التي تمكّن التفاعل بين أجهزة المحمول والتليفزيون.</Arabic>
			<ArabicEgypt>يوفر لك متجر التطبيقات أكثر من 300+ تطبيق وتتراوح التطبيقات بين تطبيقات الفيديو، والتطبيقات الاجتماعية، والألعاب، والموسيقى، وتطبيقات مشاركة الصور التي تمكنك أيضًا من إحداث تفاعل بين التلفاز وأجهزة المحمول.</ArabicEgypt>
			<English>App Store provides you over 300+ applications ranging from video-on-demand, social, gaming, music, and photo sharing which also enables to interact between TV and mobile devices.</English>
			<English_LA>App Store provides you over 300+ applications ranging from video-on-demand, social, gaming, music, and photo sharing which also enables to interact between TV and mobile devices.</English_LA>
			<English_NA>App Store provides you over 300+ applications ranging from video-on-demand, social, gaming, music, and photo sharing which also enables to interact between TV and mobile devices.</English_NA>
			<Chinese>Latest version App Store provides you a comprehensive range of applications, over 300+ applications ranging from video-on-demand, social, gaming, music, and photo sharing that enables interaction between TV and mobile sets.</Chinese>
			<ChineseTraditional>Latest version App Store provides you a comprehensive range of applications, over 300+ applications ranging from video-on-demand, social, gaming, music, and photo sharing that enables interaction between TV and mobile sets.</ChineseTraditional>
			<Bulgarian>Изпълнени с живот зелени поля, оптимизирани, отчетливи цветове на стадиони и мощен звуков съраунд ефект</Bulgarian>
			<Croatian>Živahno zeleno polje, boja terena za sport optimizirana oštrinom i snažan efekt surround zvuka </Croatian>
			<Czech>Svěže zelené hřiště, optimalizovaná ostrost barvy stadionu a výkonný prostorový zvukový efekt</Czech>
			<Danish>Levende, skarpe og optimerede stadiumfarver og kraftig surround-lydeffekt</Danish>
			<Dutch>Heldere groengevulde, voor scherpte geoptimaliseerde stadiumkleur en krachtig surround geluidseffect</Dutch>
			<Estonian>Erkroheline väljak, teravus, optimaalsetes värvides staadion ja võimas surround heli </Estonian>
			<Finnish>Vivahteikkaat vihreät kentät, optimoidut stadionien värit ja tehokkaat Surround-äänitehosteet</Finnish>
			<French>App Store vous fournit plus de 300 applications pour la vidéo à la demande, le social, les jeux, la musique et le partage de photos, et celles-ci permettent l'interaction entre la télévision et les appareils mobiles.</French>
			<German>Lebendiges grünes Spielfeld, optimierte scharfe Stadionfarben und leistungsstarker Surround Sound</German>
			<Greek>Ζωντανό πράσινο στο γρασίδι, βελτιωμένη χρώματα γηπέδου και πανίσχυρα εφέ ήχου surround</Greek>
			<Hungarian>Élénkzöld pálya, a stadion színeihez igazított élesség és erőteljes surround hanghatás</Hungarian>
			<Hebrew>האפ-סטור מציעה לך למעלה מ-300 יישומונים החל מוידיאו בהזמנה, מדיה חברתית, גיימינג ושיתוף מוסיקה ותמונות שגם מאפשרים תקשורת בין מכשירי טלוויזיה למכשירים ניידים.</Hebrew>
			<Indonesian>App Store menawarkan kepada Anda lebih dari 300 pilihan aplikasi, dari video atas permintaan, sosial, permainan, musik, dan berbagi foto yang memungkinkan interaksi antara TV dan perangkat bergerak</Indonesian>
			<Italian>Campi di un verde vivido, colori dello stadio ottimizzati per una nitidezza insuperabile e incredibili effetti del suono surround </Italian>
			<Latvian>Spilgts zaļais laukums, optimizēts asums, stadiona krāsa un spēcīgs aptverošās skaņas efekts</Latvian>
			<Lithuanian>Ryškiai žalia optimizuoto kontrasto stadiono spalva ir galingas erdvinio garso efektas. </Lithuanian>
			<Mongolian>App Store танд хамгийн эрэлттэй бичлэг, нийгмийн сүлжээ, тоглоом, хөгжим, телевиз, зөөврийн төхөөрөмж хооронд холбож ашиглах боломжтой зураг хуваалцах зэрэг 300+ гаруй аппликейшн санал болгодог.</Mongolian>
			<Norwegian>Levende grønnfarger, optimaliserte fargestadier og skarphet og kraftig surroundlyd-effekt </Norwegian>
			<Persian>فروشگاه نرم افزار بیش از 300 نرم افزار در زمینه هائی چون ویدیوهای اختصاصی، رسانه های اجتماعی، بازی، موسیقی و اشتراک گذاری عکس را در اختیار شما می گذارد که امکان تعامل میان تلویزیون و دستگاه های موبایل با فراهم می آورد.</Persian>
			<Polish>Wyrazista zieleń boiska, zoptymalizowana ostrość kolorów stadionu oraz potężny dźwięk surround </Polish>
			<Portuguese>A loja de aplicações disponibiliza mais de 300 aplicações de vídeos a pedido, redes sociais, jogos, música e de partilha de fotos que permitem igualmente fazer a interação entre a TV e os dispositivos móveis.</Portuguese>
			<Portuguese_LA>A Loja de Apps oferece a você mais de 300 aplicativos, como apps de vídeo sob demanda, sociais, de jogos, música e de compartilhamento de fotos, que também permitem a interação entre a TV e dispositivos móveis.</Portuguese_LA>
			<Romanian>Câmpuri de un verde viu, culoare şi claritate a stadionului optimizate şi efect surround redutabil</Romanian>
			<Russian>App Store предлагает вам более 300 приложений, включая видео-по-запросу, социальные, игровые и музыкальные программы, а также приложения для обмена фотографиями, которые также обеспечивают интерактивную связь между телевизором и мобильными устройствами.</Russian>
			<Serbian>Živopisni zeleni tereni, boje sa stadiona optimizovane u pogledu oštrine i snažni efekti okružujućeg zvuka</Serbian>
			<Slovak>Živé ihrisko, ostrosť optimalizovaná pre farby štadiónov a silný efekt priestorového zvuku</Slovak>
			<Slovenian>Živo zeleno igrišče, optimizirana ostrina barve stadiona in zmogljiv prostorski zvočni učinek</Slovenian>
			<Spanish>App Store le ofrece más de 300 aplicaciones que van desde videos a la carta, sociales, juegos, música e intercambio de fotografías. También permite la interacción entre la televisión y los dispositivos móviles.</Spanish>
			<Spanish_LA>App Store le ofrece más de 300 aplicaciones que van desde videos a la carta, sociales, juegos, música e intercambio de fotografías. También permite la interacción entre la televisión y los dispositivos móviles.</Spanish_LA>
			<Spanish_NA>App Store le ofrece más de 300 aplicaciones que van desde videos a la carta, sociales, juegos, música e intercambio de fotografías. También permite la interacción entre la televisión y los dispositivos móviles.</Spanish_NA>
			<Swedish>Levande grön, arktiverad, optimerad stadium med skäpa och kraftfullt surroundljud</Swedish>
			<Turkish>Canlı yeşil saha, keskinliği optimize edilmiş stadyum rengi ve güçlü çevresel ses efekti</Turkish>
			<Thai>App Store ช่วยให้คุณเข้าถึงแอพพลิเคชั่นกว่า 300 รายการนับจากวิดีโอตามต้องการ สื่อสังคม เกม ดนตรี และแชร์รูปภาพ ซึ่งช่วยให้คุณโต้ตอบระหว่างทีวีกับอุปกรณ์มือถือ</Thai>
			<Ukrainian>Яскраве зелене поле, колір стадіону з оптимізованою різкістю та потужний ефект об’ємного звуку</Ukrainian>
			<Uzbek>App Store sizga talabga-ko‘ra-video, ijtimoiy tarmoqlar, o‘yinlar, musiqa va fotosuratlarni baham ko‘rish kabi 300 dan ortiq ilovalarni taqdim etadi, ular TV hamda mobil qurilmalar bilan o‘zaro aloqa qilishga ham imkon beradi.</Uzbek>
			<Vietnamese>App Store mang đến hơn 300 ứng dụng từ ứng dụng xem video theo yêu cầu, mạng xã hội, trò chơi, âm nhạc và chia sẻ ảnh cho phép tương tác giữa TV và thiết bị di động.</Vietnamese>
		</description>
	</icon>

	<icon id = "Freeview+">
		<img_L>../images/esticker/Esticker_freeview+_B_l.png</img_L>
		<img_R>../images/esticker/Esticker_freeview+_B_r.png</img_R>
		<img_S>../images/esticker/esticker_freeviewplus.png</img_S>
		<title>
			<Arabic>Freeview+</Arabic>
			<ArabicEgypt>Freeview+</ArabicEgypt>
			<English>Freeview+</English>
			<English_LA>Freeview+</English_LA>
			<English_NA>Freeview+</English_NA>
			<Chinese>Freeview+</Chinese>
			<ChineseTraditional>Freeview+</ChineseTraditional>
			<Bulgarian>Freeview+</Bulgarian>
			<Croatian>Freeview+</Croatian>
			<Czech>Freeview+</Czech>
			<Danish>Freeview+</Danish>
			<Dutch>Freeview+</Dutch>
			<Estonian>Freeview+</Estonian>
			<Finnish>Freeview+</Finnish>
			<French>Freeview+</French>
			<German>Freeview+</German>
			<Greek>Freeview+</Greek>
			<Hungarian>Freeview+</Hungarian>
			<Hebrew>Freeview+</Hebrew>
			<Indonesian>Freeview+</Indonesian>
			<Italian>Freeview+</Italian>
			<Latvian>Freeview+</Latvian>
			<Lithuanian>Freeview+</Lithuanian>
			<Mongolian>Freeview+</Mongolian>
			<Norwegian>Freeview+</Norwegian>
			<Persian>Freeview+</Persian>
			<Polish>Freeview+</Polish>
			<Portuguese>Freeview+</Portuguese>
			<Portuguese_LA>Freeview+</Portuguese_LA>
			<Romanian>Freeview+</Romanian>
			<Russian>Freeview+</Russian>
			<Serbian>Freeview+</Serbian>
			<Slovak>Freeview+</Slovak>
			<Slovenian>Freeview+</Slovenian>
			<Spanish>Freeview+</Spanish>
			<Spanish_LA>Freeview+</Spanish_LA>
			<Spanish_NA>Freeview+</Spanish_NA>
			<Swedish>Freeview+</Swedish>
			<Turkish>Freeview+</Turkish>
			<Ukrainian>Freeview+</Ukrainian>
			<Thai>Freeview+</Thai>
			<Uzbek>Freeview+</Uzbek>
			<Vietnamese>Freeview+</Vietnamese>
		</title>
		<description>
			<Arabic>مع فري فيو بلس Freeview Plus، يمكنك اللحاق بعروضك المفضلة ولا تفوت أي شيء! راجع الميزة الجديدة My TV وهي عبارة عن شاشة تليفزيون مخصصة لك لاكتشاف البرامج.</Arabic>
			<ArabicEgypt>باستخدام Freeview Plus، يمكنك متابعة برامجك المفضلة ولن تفوت أي شيء! تحقق من الميزة الجديدة "تلفازي" وهي شاشة تلفاز مخصصة لك لاكتشاف البرامج.</ArabicEgypt>
			<English>With Freeview Plus, you can catch up on your favourite shows and never miss a thing! Check out the new feature My TV that is your own dedicated TV screen for program discovery.</English>
			<English_LA>With Freeview Plus, you can catch up on your favourite shows and never miss a thing! Check out the new feature My TV that is your own dedicated TV screen for program discovery.</English_LA>
			<English_NA>With Freeview Plus, you can catch up on your favourite shows and never miss a thing! Check out the new feature My TV that is your own dedicated TV screen for program discovery.</English_NA>
			<Chinese>With Freeview Plus, you can catch up on your favourite shows and never miss a thing! Check out the new feature My TV that is your own dedicated TV screen for program discovery.</Chinese>
			<ChineseTraditional>With Freeview Plus, you can catch up on your favourite shows and never miss a thing! Check out the new feature My TV that is your own dedicated TV screen for program discovery.</ChineseTraditional>
			<Bulgarian>Изпълнени с живот зелени поля, оптимизирани, отчетливи цветове на стадиони и мощен звуков съраунд ефект</Bulgarian>
			<Croatian>Živahno zeleno polje, boja terena za sport optimizirana oštrinom i snažan efekt surround zvuka </Croatian>
			<Czech>Svěže zelené hřiště, optimalizovaná ostrost barvy stadionu a výkonný prostorový zvukový efekt</Czech>
			<Danish>Levende, skarpe og optimerede stadiumfarver og kraftig surround-lydeffekt</Danish>
			<Dutch>Heldere groengevulde, voor scherpte geoptimaliseerde stadiumkleur en krachtig surround geluidseffect</Dutch>
			<Estonian>Erkroheline väljak, teravus, optimaalsetes värvides staadion ja võimas surround heli </Estonian>
			<Finnish>Vivahteikkaat vihreät kentät, optimoidut stadionien värit ja tehokkaat Surround-äänitehosteet</Finnish>
			<French>Avec Freeview Plus, vous pouvez visionner vos émissions préférées à tout moment et ne jamais rien manquer! Jetez un coup d’œil à la nouvelle fonctionnalité My TV, un écran de télévision personnel dédié à la découverte de programmes.</French>
			<German>Lebendiges grünes Spielfeld, optimierte scharfe Stadionfarben und leistungsstarker Surround Sound</German>
			<Greek>Ζωντανό πράσινο στο γρασίδι, βελτιωμένη χρώματα γηπέδου και πανίσχυρα εφέ ήχου surround</Greek>
			<Hungarian>Élénkzöld pálya, a stadion színeihez igazított élesség és erőteljes surround hanghatás</Hungarian>
			<Hebrew>עם Freeview Plus, תוכלו להתעדכן בתוכניות האהובות עליכם ולא להחמיץ דבר! בדקו את המאפיין החדש של "הטלוויזיה שלי" - מסך טלוויזיה אישי שלכם לאיתור תוכניות.</Hebrew>
			<Indonesian>Selalu ikuti acara kesayangan dan jangan pernah ketinggalan apa pun dengan Freeview Plus! Untuk menemukan acara, gunakan fitur baru My TV yaitu layar TV khusus Anda sendiri.</Indonesian>
			<Italian>Campi di un verde vivido, colori dello stadio ottimizzati per una nitidezza insuperabile e incredibili effetti del suono surround </Italian>
			<Latvian>Spilgts zaļais laukums, optimizēts asums, stadiona krāsa un spēcīgs aptverošās skaņas efekts</Latvian>
			<Lithuanian>Ryškiai žalia optimizuoto kontrasto stadiono spalva ir galingas erdvinio garso efektas. </Lithuanian>
			<Mongolian>Freeview Plus-ээр та өөрийн дуртай шоугаа нөхөж, алгасахгүй үзэх боломжтой.  Зөвхөн танд зориулагдсан ТВ дэлгэц болох Миний ТВ-ийн шинэ үйлдлүүдийг шалгаж, програм нээн илрүүлнэ үү.</Mongolian>
			<Norwegian>Levende grønnfarger, optimaliserte fargestadier og skarphet og kraftig surroundlyd-effekt </Norwegian>
			<Persian>با Freeview Plus می توانید تمام سریال ها و برنامه های محبوب تان را دنبال کنید و هرگز چیزی را از دست ندهید! قابلیت جدید My TV صفحه اختصاصی تلویزیونی شما برای یافتن برنامه های جدید است.</Persian>
			<Polish>Wyrazista zieleń boiska, zoptymalizowana ostrość kolorów stadionu oraz potężny dźwięk surround </Polish>
			<Portuguese>Com o Freeview Plus, você pode acompanhar seus shows favoritos e nunca perder nada! Conheça o novo recurso Minha TV, que é sua tela pessoal exclusiva de TV para descoberta de programas.</Portuguese>
			<Portuguese_LA>Com o Freeview Plus, você pode acompanhar seus shows favoritos e nunca perder nada! Conheça o novo recurso Minha TV, que é sua tela pessoal exclusiva de TV para descoberta de programas.</Portuguese_LA>
			<Romanian>Câmpuri de un verde viu, culoare şi claritate a stadionului optimizate şi efect surround redutabil</Romanian>
			<Russian>С Freeview Plus вы всегда успеете на свои любимые шоу и никогда ничего не пропустите! Ознакомьтесь с новой функцией My TV, которая позволяет завести собственную страницу на телевизоре для открытия новых программ.</Russian>
			<Serbian>Živopisni zeleni tereni, boje sa stadiona optimizovane u pogledu oštrine i snažni efekti okružujućeg zvuka</Serbian>
			<Slovak>Živé ihrisko, ostrosť optimalizovaná pre farby štadiónov a silný efekt priestorového zvuku</Slovak>
			<Slovenian>Živo zeleno igrišče, optimizirana ostrina barve stadiona in zmogljiv prostorski zvočni učinek</Slovenian>
			<Spanish>¡Con Freeview Plus, puedes ponerte al corriente con tus programas favoritos y nunca te perderás de nada! Prueba la nueva función My TV, que es tu propia pantalla de TV dedicada a la exploración de programas.</Spanish>
			<Spanish_LA>¡Con Freeview Plus, puedes ponerte al corriente con tus programas favoritos y nunca te perderás de nada! Prueba la nueva función My TV, que es tu propia pantalla de TV dedicada a la exploración de programas.</Spanish_LA>
			<Spanish_NA>¡Con Freeview Plus, puedes ponerte al corriente con tus programas favoritos y nunca te perderás de nada! Prueba la nueva función My TV, que es tu propia pantalla de TV dedicada a la exploración de programas.</Spanish_NA>
			<Swedish>Levande grön, arktiverad, optimerad stadium med skäpa och kraftfullt surroundljud</Swedish>
			<Turkish>Canlı yeşil saha, keskinliği optimize edilmiş stadyum rengi ve güçlü çevresel ses efekti</Turkish>
			<Thai>เมื่อใช้ Freeview Plus คุณสามารถติดตามรายการโปรดของคุณและไม่พลาดรายการใดเลย ลองใช้คุณสมบัติใหม่ My TV ซึ่งเป็นหน้าจอทีวีของคุณโดยเฉพาะสำหรับการค้นหารายการ</Thai>
			<Ukrainian>Яскраве зелене поле, колір стадіону з оптимізованою різкістю та потужний ефект об’ємного звуку</Ukrainian>
			<Uzbek>Freeview Plus bilan siz sevimli shoularingizni ko‘rishingiz mumkin va biror narsani ham o‘tkazib yubormaysiz! Dasturlarni kashf qilish uchun sizga mo‘ljallangan TV ekran bo‘lgan yangi Mening TV xususiyatini tekshiring.</Uzbek>
			<Vietnamese>Với Freeview Plus, bạn luôn có thể theo dõi các chương trình yêu thích mà không hề bỏ sót! Kiểm nghiệm tính năng mới My TV, màn hình TV dành riêng cho bạn để khám phá các chương trình.</Vietnamese>
		</description>
	</icon>

	<icon id = "T-Cast">
		<img_L>../images/esticker/Esticker_T-cast_B_l.png</img_L>
		<img_R>../images/esticker/Esticker_T-cast_B_r.png</img_R>
		<img_S>../images/esticker/esticker_tcast.png</img_S>
		<title>
			<Arabic>T-Cast</Arabic>
			<ArabicEgypt>T-Cast</ArabicEgypt>
			<English>T-Cast</English>
			<English_LA>T-Cast</English_LA>
			<English_NA>T-Cast</English_NA>
			<Chinese>T-Cast</Chinese>
			<ChineseTraditional>T-Cast</ChineseTraditional>
			<Bulgarian>T-Cast</Bulgarian>
			<Croatian>T-Cast</Croatian>
			<Czech>T-Cast</Czech>
			<Danish>T-Cast</Danish>
			<Dutch>T-Cast</Dutch>
			<Estonian>T-Cast</Estonian>
			<Finnish>T-Cast</Finnish>
			<French>T-Cast</French>
			<German>T-Cast</German>
			<Greek>T-Cast</Greek>
			<Hungarian>T-Cast</Hungarian>
			<Hebrew>T-Cast</Hebrew>
			<Indonesian>T-Cast</Indonesian>
			<Italian>T-Cast</Italian>
			<Latvian>T-Cast</Latvian>
			<Lithuanian>T-Cast</Lithuanian>
			<Mongolian>T-Кэст</Mongolian>
			<Norwegian>T-Cast</Norwegian>
			<Persian>T-Cast</Persian>
			<Polish>T-Cast</Polish>
			<Portuguese>T-Cast</Portuguese>
			<Portuguese_LA>T-Cast</Portuguese_LA>
			<Romanian>T-Cast</Romanian>
			<Russian>T-Cast</Russian>
			<Serbian>T-Cast</Serbian>
			<Slovak>T-Cast</Slovak>
			<Slovenian>T-Cast</Slovenian>
			<Spanish>T-Cast</Spanish>
			<Spanish_LA>T-Cast</Spanish_LA>
			<Spanish_NA>T-Cast</Spanish_NA>
			<Swedish>T-Cast</Swedish>
			<Turkish>T-Cast</Turkish>
			<Ukrainian>T-Cast</Ukrainian>
			<Thai>T-Cast</Thai>
			<Uzbek>T-Cast</Uzbek>
			<Vietnamese>T-Cast</Vietnamese>
		</title>
		<description>
			<Arabic>مع T-Cast يمكنك تشغيل جهاز التليفزيون باستخدام الهاتف الذكي، كما يمكن عرض محتوى المحمول على شاشة التليفزيون ومحتوى التليفزيون على الجهاز المحمول، مع أفضل تجربة للتسلية بدون توقف.</Arabic>
			<ArabicEgypt>تسمح لك خاصية T-Cast بتشغيل التلفاز باستخدام هاتف ذكي، وأن تكون قادرًا على بث محتويات الهاتف المحمول على شاشة التلفاز وبث محتوى التلفاز على الجهاز المحمول، والاستمتاع بأفضل تجربة ترفيه دائمة أكثر من أي وقت مضى.</ArabicEgypt>
			<English>T-Cast allows to operate TV by using smartphone, be able to cast mobile contents to TV screen and TV content to mobile device, best experience with non-stopped entertainment ever.</English>
			<English_LA>T-Cast allows to operate TV by using smartphone, be able to cast mobile contents to TV screen and TV content to mobile device, best experience with non-stopped entertainment ever.</English_LA>
			<English_NA>T-Cast allows to operate TV by using smartphone, be able to cast mobile contents to TV screen and TV content to mobile device, best experience with non-stopped entertainment ever.</English_NA>
			<Chinese>Simply watch your photos, videos and music from your Smart phone, PC, Hard Drives and other devices (connected to your wireless home network) directly on your Smart TV.</Chinese>
			<ChineseTraditional>Simply watch your photos, videos and music from your Smart phone, PC, Hard Drives and other devices (connected to your wireless home network) directly on your Smart TV.</ChineseTraditional>
			<Bulgarian>2K интерполацията на кадрите и фоновото осветление се справят ефективно с размазването на движенията.</Bulgarian>
			<Croatian>2K okvirna interpolacija i svijetlost u pozadini, pazeći da se eliminira zamućenje u pokretu. </Croatian>
			<Czech>Interpolace rámu 2K a podsvícení proti problémům s rozostřením při pohybu.</Czech>
			<Danish>2K indrammet interpolation og baggrundsbelysning til bekæmpelse af sløringsproblemer.</Danish>
			<Dutch>2K frame interpolatie en achtergrondverlichting als bestrijding van het vervagen van beweging.</Dutch>
			<Estonian>2K kaadri interpolatsioon ja taustvalgustus võitlevad liikumishägu probleemidega.</Estonian>
			<Finnish>2K ruudun interpolointi ja takavalo sumennuksen estoon.</Finnish>
			<French>La meilleure expérience en matière de divertissement sans interruption, T-Cast permet de contrôler le téléviseur depuis un téléphone intelligent, de diffuser du contenu mobile sur l'écran du téléviseur ou le contenu du téléviseur sur un appareil mobile.</French>
			<German>2K Frame-Interpolation und Hintergrundbeleuchtung gegen Probleme mit der Bewegungsunschärfe.</German>
			<Greek>Η λειτουργία παρεμβολής καρέ 2K και ο οπίσθιος φωτισμός εξαλείφει τη θαμπάδα από την κινούμενη εικόνα.</Greek>
			<Hungarian>A 2K keret interpoláció és háttérvilágítás a képen jelentkező foltproblémák eltüntetéséhez.</Hungarian>
			<Hebrew>T-Cast תאפשר לך להפעיל את הטלוויזיה באמצעות הטלפון החכם, להעביר תוכן סלולארי למסך הטלוויזיה ותוכן טלוויזיוני למכשיר הנייד ותעניק לך חוויה של בידור שלא נגמר.</Hebrew>
			<Indonesian>Dengan T-Cast, Anda dapat mengoperasikan TV lewat ponsel pintar, menyiarkan konten seluler ke layar TV dan konten TV ke perangkat seluler, pengalaman terbaik dengan hiburan yang tak pernah habis.</Indonesian>
			<Italian>Interpolazione con struttura a 2K e retroilluminazione portano a problemi di offuscamento durante le scene di combattimento.</Italian>
			<Latvian>2K kadru interpolācija un aizmugurgaismojuma vadība, lai apkarotu kustības izraisītu defektu problēmas.</Latvian>
			<Lithuanian>2K rėmelio interpoliacija ir apšvietimas išvengti išliejimo problemų.</Lithuanian>
			<Mongolian>T-Cast нь танд ухаалаг утсаа ашиглан ТВ-гээ удирдах буюу гар утсан дээрх контентыг ТВ-н дэлгэц дээр гаргах, ТВ контентыг гар утсан дээр гаргах боломж олгодог ба та энтертейнмэнт контентоо тасралтгүйгээр үзэн хамгийн сайхан мэдрэмж авах болно.</Mongolian>
			<Norwegian>2K ramme-interpolering og bakgrunnsbelysning for å redusere problemer med bevegelsesuskarphet.</Norwegian>
			<Persian>با T-Cast می توانید تلویزیون را با استفاده از تلفن هوشمند به کار اندازید، برنامه ها را از روی موبایل روی صفحه تلویزیون و بلعکس از تلویزیون روی صفحه موبایل نمایش داده و  از برترین تجربه تفریحات و سرگرمی تمام نشدنی لذت ببرید.</Persian>
			<Polish>Interpolacja klatek 2K i podświetlenie eliminują problem rozmazanych ruchów.</Polish>
			<Portuguese>O T-Cast permite controlar a TV a partir do smartphone e transmitir conteúdos do dispositivo móvel para o ecrã da TV e desta para o dispositivo móvel; é a melhor experiência de entretenimento contínuo de sempre.</Portuguese>
			<Portuguese_LA>O T-Cast permite controlar a TV usando um dispositivo móvel, possibilitando a transmissão de conteúdos desse dispositivo para a tela da TV e vice-versa, o que proporciona a melhor experiência sem interrupção na diversão.</Portuguese_LA>
			<Romanian>Interpolare de cadru 2K şi redare în fundal pentru a combate neclaritatea de mişcare.</Romanian>
			<Russian>Функция T-Cast позволяет управлять телевизором с помощью смартфона и дает возможность предать контент с мобильного устройства на экран телевизора, а также контент с телевизора на мобильное устройство. Надеемся, что эта новая возможность доставит вам истинное удовольствие.</Russian>
			<Serbian>2K okvirna interpolacija i svetlost u pozadini, pazeći da se eliminiše zamućenje u pokretu.</Serbian>
			<Slovak>Interpolácia rámu 2K a podsvietenie proti problémom s rozostrením pri pohybu.</Slovak>
			<Slovenian>2K interpolacija okvirja in ovetlitev v ozadju, ki skrbi za odpravljanje zamegljenosti pri gibanju.</Slovenian>
			<Spanish>T-Cast permite operar la televisión mediante el uso de teléfonos inteligentes. Transmite contenido móvil a la pantalla de televisión y contenido de TV a dispositivos móviles para ofrecerte la mejor experiencia de entretenimiento sin parar.</Spanish>
			<Spanish_LA>T-Cast permite operar la televisión mediante el uso de teléfonos inteligentes. Transmite contenido móvil a la pantalla de televisión y contenido de TV a dispositivos móviles para ofrecerte la mejor experiencia de entretenimiento sin parar.</Spanish_LA>
			<Spanish_NA>T-Cast permite operar la televisión mediante el uso de teléfonos inteligentes. Transmite contenido móvil a la pantalla de televisión y contenido de TV a dispositivos móviles para ofrecerte la mejor experiencia de entretenimiento sin parar.</Spanish_NA>
			<Swedish>2K bild interpolation och bakgrundsbelysning för motverkande av problem med rörelseoskärpa. </Swedish>
			<Turkish>2K çerçeve enterpolasyonu ve arka aydınlatma hareket bulanıklığı sorunlarıyla baş eder.</Turkish>
			<Thai>T-Cast ช่วยให้คุณดูทีวีโดยใช้สมาร์ทโฟน สามารถคาสต์เนื้อหามือถือไปยังหน้าจอทีวี และเนื้อหาทีวีไปยังอุปกรณ์มือถือ รับประสบการณ์ที่ดีที่สุดกับความบันเทิงไร้ขีดจำกัด</Thai>
			<Ukrainian>Кадрова інтерполяція 4К і драйвери заднього підсвічування допомагають боротися з розмиттям.</Ukrainian>
			<Uzbek>T-Cast smartfondan foydalanib TV ni ishlatish, mobil kontentlarni TV ekraniga va TV kontentlarni mobil qurilmaga uzatishga imkon beradi va bu misli ko‘rilmagan ko‘ngilochar dasturli eng yaxshi tajribadir.</Uzbek>
			<Vietnamese>T-Cast cho phép sử dụng TV bằng điện thoại thông minh, nhờ đó bạn có thể chiếu các nội dung trên điện thoại lên màn hình TV và nội dung trên TV trên thiết bị di động, mang đến trải nghiệm giải trí không ngừng nghỉ tuyệt vời nhất.</Vietnamese>
		</description>
	</icon>

	<icon id = "Sports Mode">
		<img_L>../images/esticker/Esticker_Sports Mode_B_l.png</img_L>
		<img_R>../images/esticker/Esticker_Sports Mode_B_r.png</img_R>
		<img_S>../images/esticker/esticker_sportsmode.png</img_S>
		<title>
			<Arabic>وضع الرياضة</Arabic>
			<ArabicEgypt>وضع الرياضة</ArabicEgypt>
			<English>Sports Mode</English>
			<English_LA>Sports Mode</English_LA>
			<English_NA>Sports Mode</English_NA>
			<Chinese>Sports Mode</Chinese>
			<ChineseTraditional>Sports Mode</ChineseTraditional>
			<Bulgarian>Sports Mode</Bulgarian>
			<Croatian>Sports Mode</Croatian>
			<Czech>Sports Mode</Czech>
			<Danish>Sports Mode</Danish>
			<Dutch>Sports Mode</Dutch>
			<Estonian>Sports Mode</Estonian>
			<Finnish>Sports Mode</Finnish>
			<French>Mode Sports</French>
			<German>Sports Mode</German>
			<Greek>Sports Mode</Greek>
			<Hungarian>Sports Mode</Hungarian>
			<Hebrew>מצב ספורט</Hebrew>
			<Indonesian>Mode olahraga</Indonesian>
			<Italian>Sports Mode</Italian>
			<Latvian>Sports Mode</Latvian>
			<Lithuanian>Sports Mode</Lithuanian>
			<Mongolian>Спортын Горим</Mongolian>
			<Norwegian>Sports Mode</Norwegian>
			<Persian>حالت ورزشی</Persian>
			<Polish>Sports Mode</Polish>
			<Portuguese>Modo de esporte</Portuguese>
			<Portuguese_LA>Modo de esporte</Portuguese_LA>
			<Romanian>Sports Mode</Romanian>
			<Russian>Режим «Спорт»</Russian>
			<Serbian>Sports Mode</Serbian>
			<Slovak>Sports Mode</Slovak>
			<Slovenian>Sports Mode</Slovenian>
			<Spanish>Modo Deportes</Spanish>
			<Spanish_LA>Modo Deportes</Spanish_LA>
			<Spanish_NA>Modo Deportes</Spanish_NA>
			<Swedish>Sports Mode</Swedish>
			<Turkish>Sports Mode</Turkish>
			<Ukrainian>Sports Mode</Ukrainian>
			<Thai>โหมดกีฬา</Thai>
			<Uzbek>Sport rejimi</Uzbek>
			<Vietnamese>Chế độ thể thao</Vietnamese>
		</title>
		<description>
			<Arabic>يتيح تحسين الصوت والصورة للجمهور الاستمتاع بالشعور الغامر للأحداث الرياضية المباشرة. </Arabic>
			<ArabicEgypt>تمكن خاصية تحسين الصور والصوت الجمهور من الاستمتاع بشعور الانغماس في الأحداث الرياضية المثيرة.</ArabicEgypt>
			<English>The optimization of images and sound allows audiences to enjoy the immersive feeling of live-action sports events.</English>
			<English_LA>The optimization of images and sound allows audiences to enjoy the immersive feeling of live-action sports events.</English_LA>
			<English_NA>The optimization of images and sound allows audiences to enjoy the immersive feeling of live-action sports events.</English_NA>
			<Chinese>The optimization of images and sound allows audiences to enjoy the immersive feeling of live-action sports events.</Chinese>
			<ChineseTraditional>The optimization of images and sound allows audiences to enjoy the immersive feeling of live-action sports events.</ChineseTraditional>
			<Bulgarian>FreeviewPlus осигурява безпроблемен достъп до всички налични Catch Up TV програми от мрежите с безплатно излъчване.</Bulgarian>
			<Croatian>FreeviewPlus omogućuje bešavni pristup svim dostupnim Catch Up TV kanalima u nekodiranim mrežama.</Croatian>
			<Czech>FreeviewPlus poskytuje bezproblémový přístup ke všem dostupným Catch Up TV ze sítí pro bezplatné vysílání.</Czech>
			<Danish>FreeviewPlus giver sømløs adgang til alle tilgængelige Catch-Up TV-udsendelser fra free-to-air-netværkene.</Danish>
			<Dutch>FreeviewPlus biedt naadloze toegang tot alle beschikbare Catch Up TV van de vrij te ontvangen netwerken. </Dutch>
			<Estonian>FreeviewPlus pakub sujuvat ligipääsu kogu saadavale Catch Up TV-le vabalevi võrkudest.</Estonian>
			<Finnish>FreeviewPlus tarjoaa saumattoman pääsyn kaikkiin käytettävissä oleviin Internet-TV-kanaviin ilmaisissa verkoissa.</Finnish>
			<French>L’optimalisation d’images et de sons permet aux audiences d’apprécier le sentiment immersif des événements sportifs en direct.</French>
			<German>FreeviewPlus bietet von allen kostenlosten Netzwerken reibungslosen Zugriff auf alle verfügbaren Catch Up Fernsehsendungen.</German>
			<Greek>Το FreeviewPlus παρέχει άμεση πρόσβαση σε όλα τα διαθέσιμα τηλεοπτικά κανάλια ελεύθερης λήψης.</Greek>
			<Hungarian>A FreeviewPlus szolgáltatással zökkenőmentesen elérhető az ingyenesen nézhető hálózatok minden Catc Up TV csatornája.</Hungarian>
			<Hebrew>אופטימיזציה של התמונות והצלילים מאפשרת לקהלים ליהנות מתחושת המצאת באירוע ספורט חי. </Hebrew>
			<Indonesian>Dengan optimisasi gambar dan suara, penonton seolah terlibat langsung dalam acara olahraga penuh aksi.</Indonesian>
			<Italian>FreeviewPlus consente l’accesso immediato a tutti i canali Catch Up TV disponibili delle reti in chiaro.</Italian>
			<Latvian>FreeviewPlus nodrošina vienotu piekļuvi visām pieejamajām Catch Up TV programmām no bezmaksas (free-to-air) tīkliem.</Latvian>
			<Lithuanian>FreeviewPlus“ suteikia tiesioginę prieigą prie  visos prieinamos po premjeros rodomos TV iš nemokamų tinklų. </Lithuanian>
			<Mongolian>Спортын тоглолтуудыг амьдаар-үзэж буй мэт бодит мэдрэмжийг үзэгчдэд мэдрүүлэх дээд зэргийн зураг дүрс болон дууны тохируулга.</Mongolian>
			<Norwegian>FreeviewPlus gir sømløs tilgang til Catch Up TV som er tilgjengelig fra kringkastingsberettigede nettverk.</Norwegian>
			<Persian>بهینه سازی تصاویر و صداها به مخاطبان اجازه می دهد تا از حس فراگیر رویدادهای ورزشی زنده لذت ببرند.</Persian>
			<Polish>FreeviewPlus zapewnia ciągły dostęp do wszystkich dostępnych programów Catch Up TV z ogólnodostępnych sieci.</Polish>
			<Portuguese>A otimização de imagens e som permite que as pessoas sintam a sensação de envolvimento em eventos esportivos ao vivo.</Portuguese>
			<Portuguese_LA>A otimização de imagens e som permite que as pessoas sintam a sensação de envolvimento em eventos esportivos ao vivo.</Portuguese_LA>
			<Romanian>FreeviewPlus oferă acces direct la toate emisiunile TV la cerere ale posturilor cu difuzare gratuită. </Romanian>
			<Russian>Оптимизация изображения и звука позволяет зрителям по-настоящему погрузиться в динамичную атмосферу спортивных событий. </Russian>
			<Serbian>FreeviewPlus nudi nesmetan pristup svim dostupnim Catch Up TV iz slobodnih mreža.</Serbian>
			<Slovak>FreeViewPlus poskytuje bezproblémový prístup ku všetkým Catch Up TV z bezplatných sietí.</Slovak>
			<Slovenian>FreeviewPlus vam nudi neomejen dostop do vseh Catch up TV programov, ki so na voljo preko nekodiranih omrežij.</Slovenian>
			<Spanish>La optimización de imágenes y sonido les permite a las audiencias disfrutar de la sensación estar en los eventos deportivos en vivo.</Spanish>
			<Spanish_LA>La optimización de imágenes y sonido les permite a las audiencias disfrutar de la sensación estar en los eventos deportivos en vivo.</Spanish_LA>
			<Spanish_NA>La optimización de imágenes y sonido les permite a las audiencias disfrutar de la sensación estar en los eventos deportivos en vivo.</Spanish_NA>
			<Swedish>FreeviewPlus erbjuder sömlös åtkomst till alla tillgängliga Catch Up TV från gratis nätverk.</Swedish>
			<Turkish>FreeviewPlus ücretsiz yayın ağlarından gelen tüm mevcut Catch Up TV hizmetlerine sorunsuz erişim sunar.</Turkish>
			<Thai>การปรับภาพและเสียงให้เหมาะที่สุดช่วยให้ผู้ชมเพลิดเพลินและดื่มด่ำไปกับรายการกีฬาที่ให้ภาพสมจริง</Thai>
			<Ukrainian>FreeviewPlus надає безперешкодний доступ до всіх каналів з вільно трансльованих мереж, доступних у форматі «слідом за ефіром».</Ukrainian>
			<Uzbek>Tasvirlar va tovushni optimallashtirish tomoshabinlarni jonli sport o‘yinlarining qamrab oluvchi hissiyotlaridan rohatlanishlariga imkon beradi. </Uzbek>
			<Vietnamese>Tính năng tối ưu hóa hình ảnh và âm thanh cho phép người xem đắm chìm vào cảm giác trung thực của các sự kiện thể thao trực tiếp.</Vietnamese>
		</description>
	</icon>
</root>